A Guide to the Executive Papers of Governor Harry F. Byrd, 1926-1930
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
A Guide to the Executive Papers of Governor Harry F. Byrd, 1926-1930
The Library of Virginia
22561
70 cu. ft. (140 boxes)
Byrd, Harry Flood, Records of Virginia Governor
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Transferred from the Office of the Secretary of the Commonwealth, 18 May 1939.
Biographical Information
Harry F. Byrd, Sr., was born in Martinsburg, West Virginia on 10 June 1887. He served as Governor of Virginia (1926-1930) and United States Senator (1933-1965). He died in Berryville, Virginia, 20 October 1966.
Scope and Content
Governor Harry F. Byrd Executive Papers, 1926-1930 (bulk 1922-1926), are organized into two series. Series have been designated for I. Subject Files; and Series II: Pardons, Requisitions, and Prison Affairs. These papers mainly consist of incoming and outgoing correspondence during Harry F. Byrd's four-year term as governor between 1 February 1926 and 1 February 1930. The largest and most significant series is the Subject Files Series. This series provides an in-depth look into the major concerns confronting Byrd as governor. The Pardons, Requisitions, and Prison Affairs Series includes applications, correspondence, extraditions, pardons and requisitions.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I. Subject Files, 1926-1930
Series II: Pardons, Requisitions, and Prison Affairs, 1926-1930
Contents List
- Series I: Subject files, 1926-1930., Extent: 39.75 cu. ft. (106 boxes). (Box Boxes 1-105, 141)
  The Subject files series, 1926-1930 is housed in one hundred and six archival boxes and is arranged alphabetically by subject. This series documents correspondence received and sent by Governor Byrd during his four-year term as governor of Virginia. In addition to correspondence, there are reports, proclamations, telegrams, orders, resolutions, acts, publications, news clippings, invitations, proceedings, financial statements, invoices, and other sundry items. Topics include Aviation and establishment of the Airport Commission, Celebration of the 150th anniversary of the Virginia Bill of Rights, Chamber of Commerce, pensions for Confederate veterans, Forfeited cars used for transporting illegal alcohol, Gas taxes and prices, Eastern State Hospital, the Jefferson memorial and centennial celebration, building of a statue for Robert E. Lee, Letters encouraging residents from other states to move to Virginia, Motion picture censorship, Motor Vehicle Commission, Norfolk and Western Railway, Oysters and shellfish, Penitentiary, Reorganization of Virginia state government, State Board of Education, Virginia Commission for the Blind, Virginia Industrial School for Colored Girls, War Memorial Commission, among others.
  Of note are the papers relating to lynchings in Virginia and Governor's Byrd efforts to have one of the toughest anti-lynching laws in the country. Included is correspondence with Louis Isaac Jaffee (1888-1950), who won the Pulitizer Prize for Editorial Writing in 1929 for his editorial, "An unspeakable act of savagery," in the Norfolk Virginian Pilot. There are also letters relating to a lynching in Wytheville, Virginia, and the appointment of a special prosecutor for the case.
  Of note are the papers relating to the State Commission of Conservation and Development and the creation of Shenandoah National Park. Included are minutes from the commission, letters regarding billboards on highways blocking scenery, letters of support for the National Park from politicians and citizens, maps of the proposed park, brochures, and information on Virginia historic markers. Also included is correspondence with John D. Rockefeller regarding the restoration of Colonial Williamsburg.
  Also included are appointments to various boards such as American Mining Congress, William and Mary Board of Visitors, Adjutant General, and State Board of Public Welfare.
  Also included are appointments to various boards such as the
  This series was maintained in its original order and is not completely chronological. At some point the pins holding together the incoming and outgoing letters were removed and the archivist did not rearrange the folder items for fear of loosing the relationships between the incoming and outgoing letters.
  The Pardons, Requisitions, and Prison Affairs series, 1926-1930, is housed in archival boxes and is arranged into three subseries. Subseries have been designated for A.
  Arranged alphabetically by folder title.
  - A, 1926 February - October. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - A, 1926 November - 1927 February. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - A, 1927 March - October. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - A, 1927 November - 1929 December. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Accounting system, 1925-1927. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Accountant, State, 1926-1927. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Addresses and statements, 1926 - 1927 July. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Addresses and statements, 1927 August - December. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Addresses and statements, 1928 January - April. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Addresses and statements, 1928 May - December. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Addresses and statements, 1929 January - May. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Addresses and statements, 1929 May - 1930 January. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Adjutant General, 1926. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Adjutant General, 1927. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Adjutant General, 1928. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Adjutant General, 1929. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Agriculture, Farm Commission, 1928. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Agriculture, Farm Commission, 1929 January - March. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Agriculture, Farm Commission, 1929 April - 1930 January. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Agriculture and Immigration, 1926. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Agriculture and Immigration, 1927. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Agriculture and Immigration, 1928. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Agriculture and Immigration, 1929. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Aliens, 1926. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - American Academy of Political and Social Sciences, 1926. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - American Arbitration Association, 1928-1929. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - American Chamber of Agriculture, 1929. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - American Cotton Conference, 1927. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - American Legion, 1926-1928. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - American Library Conference, 1926-1928. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - American Mining Congress, 1926. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - American Mining Congress, 1926. (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - American Mining Congress, 1927. (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - American Mining Congress, 1928. (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - American Mining Congress, 1929. (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - American Prison Association, 1926-1929. (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - American Public Health Association, 1927. (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - American Taxpayers League, 1927. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Andrews, Matthew Page, 1926-1928. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Annual reports, 1926-1930. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Anti-Saloon League Convention, 1927. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Apple Blossom Festival (Winchester, Va.), 1926-1927. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Apple Blossom Festival (Winchester, Va.), 1928. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Apple Blossom Festival (Winchester, Va.), 1929-1930. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Appointments, Misc., 1927-1928. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Appointments, by Governor, 1926-1930. (Box 5, Folder 9-10)
  - Appointments, Delegates, 1926-1930. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Appointments, Requiring confirmation, 1926-1928. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Appointments, Not requiring confirmation, 1926-1929. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Arkansas, Governor of, 1927-1929. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Arlington County, Proposed abattoir, 1929. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Arlington County, Misc., 1929-1930. (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Art Commission, 1926-1928. (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Art Commission, 1929-1930. (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Association for the Preservation of Virginia Antiquities, 1926-1929. (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Astor, Nancy Langhorne, 1926. (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Atlantic Deeper Waterways Association, 1926. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Atlantic Deeper Waterways Association, 1927. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Atlantic Deeper Waterways Association, 1928-1929. (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Attorney General, 1926. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Attorney General, 1927. (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Attorney General, 1928-1929. (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts, Annual report, 1926. (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts, 1926-1927. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts, Second, 1926-1927. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Auditing Committee, 1926-1930. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Aviation, Aeronautical School, 1929. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Aviation, Airplane letters, 1926-1929. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Aviation, Air Port Commission, 1926-1927. (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Aviation, Air Port Commission,, 1928. (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Aviation, Air Port Commission,, 1929. (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Aviation, Air Tour, 1929. (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Aviation, Aviation roof markers, 1929. (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - B, 1926 February - June. (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - B, 1926 June - September. (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - B, 1926 October - December. (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - B, 1927 January - March. (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - B, 1927 February - July. (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - B, 1927 March - April. (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - B, 1927 July - September. (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - B, 1927 October - December. (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - B, 1928. (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - B, 1929-1930. (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Beamer, B.D., 1929. (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Banking laws, Commission to codify, 1926-1928. (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Banksuit, 1927. (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Battlefield Marker Commission, 1926-1927. (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Bill of Rights Celebration, 1926. (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Books. Booklets, Acknowledgements, 1927-1929. (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Brooklyn Bridge Plaza Association, 1928. (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Budget Director, 1926-1928. (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Budget Director, 1929-1930. (Box 11, Folder 1-2)
  - Budget Conference, 1926-1927. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Building and Grounds, Superintendent of, 1926-1929. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - C, 1926 February - July. (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - C, 1926 July - December. (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - C, 1927. (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - C, 1928. (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - C, 1929-1930. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Cabinet meeting, 1929. (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Cape Henry Memorial Commission, 1927-1929. (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Capitol Building, 1927-1929. (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Capitol Police, 1926. (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Capitol Square, 1926-1929. (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Chamber of Commerce, Virginia, 1926. (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Chamber of Commerce, Virginia, 1927. (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Chamber of Commerce, Virginia, 1928. (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Chamber of Commerce, Virginia, 1929. (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Chamber of Commerce, Bristol and Richmond, Virginia, 1926-1929. (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Chamber of Commerce, Ohio, 1928-1929. (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Chamber of Commerce, Tennessee, 1929. (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Chamber of Commerce, United States, 1929. (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Chamber of Commerce, Vermont, 1929. (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Child Labor Amendment, 1926. (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - City Treasurer, Portsmouth, 1926. (Box 13, Folder 6a)
  - Colorado, 1929. (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Compensation insurance, 1926-1929. (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Children's Home Society of Virginia, 1926-1929. (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Clerks, House of Delegates, 1928-1929. (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Coal, 1926-1928. (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Commissioners of Revenue, 1928. (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Confederate Veterans, 1926-1927. (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Confederate Veterans, 1928. (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Confederate Veterans, 1929. (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Confederate women, Needy, 1926-1928. (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Conference of College Heads, 1929. (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Congress of Agriculture, 1929. (Box 13, Folder 17a)
  - Connecticut, 1929. (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Conferences, Miscellaneous, 1927-1929. (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Conservation and Development, Commission of, Advertising, 1927-1929. (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Conservation and Development, Commission of, Efficiency Industrial Bureau, 1928. (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Conservation and Development, Commission of, Geologist, 1929. (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Conservation and Development, Commission, Minutes, 1926 - 1927 June. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Conservation and Development, Commission, Minutes, 1927 July - December. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Conservation and Development, Commission, Minutes, 1928. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Conservation and Development, Commission, Minutes, 1929. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Conservation and Development, Commission, Programs, 1927 February. (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Conservation and Development, Commission, Programs, 1927 March - May. (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Conservation and Development, Commission, Programs, 1927 June - August. (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Conservation and Development, Commission, Programs, 1927 September - December. (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Conservation and Development, Commission, Programs, 1928 February - May. (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Conservation and Development, Commission, Programs, 1928 September - November. (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Conservation and Development, Commission, Programs, 1928 December. (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Conservation and Development, Commission, Programs, 1929 February - April. (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Conservation and Development, Commission, Programs, 1929 June. (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Conservation and Development, Commission, Shenandoah National Park, 1926. (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Conservation and Development, Commission, Shenandoah National Park, 1926. (Box 16, Folder 1-3a)
  - Conservation and Development, Commission, Shenandoah National Park, 1927. (Box 16, Folder 4-5)
  - Conservation and Development, Commission, Shenandoah National Park, 1928-1929. (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Conservation and Development, Commission, Miscellaneous, 1926 January - July. (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Conservation and Development, Commission, Miscellaneous, 1926 August - December. (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Conservation and Development, Commission, Miscellaneous, 1927 January - May. (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Conservation and Development, Commission, Miscellaneous, 1927 June - December. (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Conservation and Development, Commission, Miscellaneous, 1928 January - March. (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Conservation and Development, Commission, Miscellaneous, 1928 April - August. (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Conservation and Development, Commission, Miscellaneous, 1928 September - December. (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Conservation and Development, Commission, Miscellaneous, 1929 January - March. (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Conservation and Development, Commission, Miscellaneous, 1929 April - July. (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Conservation and Development, Commission, Miscellaneous, 1929 August - 1930 January. (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Constitutional Amendments, Commission, 1926-1927. (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Constitutional Amendments, Commission, 1928. (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Constitutional Amendments, Commission, Favorable replies list, ca. 1926-1928. (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Constitutional Amendments, Commission, Transcript of public hearings, 1926 October - December. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Contributions, 1928. (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Cotton, 1926. (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Cotton Conference, 1926-1928. (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - County budgets, 1926-1928. (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - County government, 1926-1927. (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - County government, 1928-1929. (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - County levies, 1928. (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - County records, 1926-1928. (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - County road plans, 1928-1929. (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - County Treasurer, Buchanon County, 1927-1928. (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - County Treasurer, James City County and Williamsburg, 1928-1929. (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - County Treasurer, Lee County, 1928. (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - County Treasurer, Norfolk, 1929. (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - County Treasurer, Southampton County, 1929. (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - County Treasurer, Warren County, 1927. (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - County Treasurer, Wise County, 1928. (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Cripple Children's Hospital, 1929. (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Cruelty to criminals, 1927. (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Cumberland Gap Pioneers, 1929. (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - D, 1926 January - June. (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - D, 1926 July - December. (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - D, 1927 January - April. (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - D, 1927 May December. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - D, 1928-1929. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Dairy Food Commission, 1926-1929. (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Data, 1929. (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Data of states, 1926-1928. (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Davis building, 1928. (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Davis, Charles Hall, 1926. (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Davis Clinic investigation, 1926-1929. (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Deeds, Commissioner of, 1926-1930. (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Delaware, 1929. (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Delegates, Miscellaneous, 1926-1929. (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Daily Cash Proof, Governor's Office, 1928 March - 1929 February. (Box 21)
  - Daily Cash Proof, Governor's Office, 1929 March - 1930 February. (Box 21)
  - E, 1926. (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - E, 1927-1929. (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Edison, Thomas A. Inc., Light's Golden Jubilee, 1929. (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Education, Cooperative Educational Association, 1926-1929. (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Education, Edison contest, 1929. (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Education, State Board of, 1928. (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Education, State Board of, 1929-1930. (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Education, State Board of, Superintendents, 1928-1929. (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Education, Study establishing Liberal Arts College for Women, 1928-1929. (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Educational survey, 1927. (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Educational survey, 1927-1929. (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Elections, 1926-1930. (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Encroachment, Waves and tides, 1928. (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Encyclopedia Britannica, 1928-1929. (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Examining Board, State Board of Accountancy, 1926-1929. (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Examining Board, State Board of Dental Examiners, 1926-1929. (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Examining Board, State Board of Embalming, 1926-1929. (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Examining Board, State Board of Graduate Nurses, 1926-1929. (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Examining Board, State Board of Medical Examiners, 1926-1928. (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Examining Board, State Board of Optometry, 1926-1929. (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Examining Board, State Board of Pharmacy, 1926-1929. (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Executive Control Fund, 1922-1929. (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - F, 1926 January - July. (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - F, 1926 August - December. (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - F, 1927 January - July. (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - F, 1927 August - 1928 June. (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - F, 1928 July - 1929 December. (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Federal census, 1929. (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Federal Farm Board, 1929. (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Federal Departments Conference, 1926. (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Federal Inheritance Tax Commission, 1926-1927. (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Federal legislation, 1927-1928. (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Federal legislation, 1928-1929. (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Federal Trade Commission, 1926. (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Fee officers, 1926-1929. (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - First landing of English Settlers, 1926. (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Fisheries, Commission of, 1926. (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Fisheries, Commission of, 1926-1927. (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Fisheries, Commission of, 1928. (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Fisheries, Commission of, 1929. (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Fisheries, Commission of, Capt. T.B. Smith, 1923-1925. (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Fisheries, Virginia Commission to confer with Maryland Commission, 1926-1929. (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Flags, 1927-1929. (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Flags, Return of Confederate flag, 1927-1928. (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Florida, 1928-1929. (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Foreign representatives, 1928. (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Forest fires, 1926. (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Forest wardens, 1926-1927. (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Forest wardens, 1928-1929. (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Forester, State, 1926-1930. (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Fort Eustis, 1929. (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - G, 1926. (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - G, 1926-1927. (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - G, 1927-1929. (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Game Commission, 1926-1929. (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Game and Inland Fisheries, 1929. (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Gasoline Tax Conference, 1928-1929. (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Gas tax distribution, 1928-1929. (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Gas tax and price, 1926 January - April. (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Gas tax and price, 1926 May - June 14. (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Gas tax and price, 1926 June 16-30. (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Gas tax and price, 1926 July - December. (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Gas tax and price, 1927 January - June. (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Gas tax and price, 1927 July - December. (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Gas tax and price, 1928-1929. (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - General Assembly, 1926. (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - General Assembly, Bills, 1926. (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - General Assembly, Messages, 1926. (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - General Assembly, New legislation, 1926. (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - General Assembly, Objections to bills, 1926. (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - General Assembly, SB 269, 1926. (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - General Assembly, SB 269, 1926. (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - General Assembly, Extra session, 1927. (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - General Assembly, Extra session, 1927. (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - General Assembly, Extra session, 1927. (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - General Assembly, Extra session, Bills, 1927. (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - General Assembly, Extra session, Messages, 1927. (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - General Assembly, 1928. (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - General Assembly, 1928. (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - General Assembly, 1928. (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - General Assembly, 1928. (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - General Assembly, Bills, 1928. (Box 31, Folder 2-5)
  - General Assembly, Committee assignments, 1928. (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - General Assembly, Downing vacancy, 1928. (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - General Assembly, HB 199, 1928. (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - General Assembly, Messages, 1928-1929. (Box 32, Folder 1-2)
  - General Assembly, Reception, 1928. (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - General Assembly, Vacancies, 1926-1929. (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - General Assembly, 1930. (Box 32, Folder 5-6)
  - General Assembly, Albemarle and Chesapeake Canal Tidal Lock, 1930. (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - General Assembly, Committee assignments, 1930. (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - General Assembly, Messages, 1930. (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - General Assembly, Reception, 1930. (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Georgia, 1927-1929. (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Good Will dinner, 1928. (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Governor's Ball, 1928. (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Governor's Conference, 1926-1927. (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Governor's Conference, 1928-1929. (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Governor's Conference, 1932. (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Governor's letters (other states), 1926. (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Governor's letters (other states), 1927. (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Governor's mansion, 1926. (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Governor's mansion, 1927-1930. (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Governor's mansion, Buffet supper, 1929. (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Governor's mansion, Reed dinner, 1929. (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Governor's mansion, Staff dinner, 1930. (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Governor's mansion, Vendor invoices, 1919-1929. (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Greetings, 1926-1927. (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - H, 1926 January - June. (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - H, 1926 June - December. (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - H, 1927 January - May. (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - H, 1927 May - August. (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - H, 1927 September - December. (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - H, 1928. (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - H, 1929-1930. (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Hall of Fame, 1927. (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Hampton Roads Port Commission, 1926. (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Health, Bureau of Vital Statistics, 1926-1929. (Box 35, Folder 5)